<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CountryProfile</string>
    <string name="Bangladesh_button">Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="India_button">India</string>
    <string name="Pakistan_button">Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Title_text">Exit</string>
    <string name="messgage_text">Are you sure, you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="Bangladesh_deatils">
        Bangladesh is a country state in Southern Asia,
        bordering the Bay of Bengal to the South,
        almost entirely encircled by the Republic of India to the West,
        North and East, and Myanmar to the Southeast.
        Although off the beaten path by virtually any measurement,
        Bangladesh is populated by friendly locals.
    </string>
    <string name="India_deatils">
       The Republic of India (Hindi: भारत गणराज्य) is a country in Asia.
        It is at the center of South Asia. India has more than
        1.2 billion (1,210,000,000) people, which is the second largest population
        in the world.[19] It is the seventh largest country in the world by
        area and the largest country in South Asia.
        It is also the most populous democracy in the world.
    </string>
    <string name="Pakistan_deatils">
       Pakistan[b] (Urdu: پاکِستان‬‎), officially the
        Islamic Republic of Pakistan (Urdu: اِسلامی جمہوریہ پاکِستان‬‎),
        is a country in South Asia. It is the fifth-most populous country
        with a population exceeding 212,742,631 people.[19] In area,
        it is the 33rd-largest country, spanning 881,913 square kilometres (340,509 square miles).
        Pakistan has a 1,046-kilometre (650-mile) coastline along
        the Arabian Sea and Gulf of Oman in the south and is bordered
        by India to the east, Afghanistan to the west, Iran to the southwest,
        and China in the far northeast. It is separated narrowly from
        Tajikistan by Afghanistan's Wakhan Corridor in the northwest,
        and also shares a maritime border with Oman.
    </string>
</resources>
